Guide to the University of Chicago Library. John Crerar Library. Records 1977-2009
University of Chicago Library
University of Chicago. Library. John Crerar Library. Records
1977-2009
24 linear feet (35 boxes)
Hanna Holborn Gray Special Collections Research Center University of Chicago Library 1100 East 57th Street Chicago, Illinois 60637 U.S.A.
This collection includes materials relating to the construction of the John Crerar Library at the University of Chicago and library activities from 1984 onwards. The majority of the material in the collection relates to the construction of the new library building, built to facilitate the transferal of the collection from the Illinois Institute of Technology to the University of Chicago campus in 1981. In addition, the collection contains materials relating to the tracking and processing of missing books during the early 1980s.
Information on Use
Access
The collection is open for research. Series V contains a restricted theft file and is closed until 2041.
Historical Note
The John Crerar Library was founded in 1894 and was initially housed in the Marshall Field Building (111 N. State Street, Chicago). By 1961 a larger space was needed to house the rapidly growing collection and a new building was constructed at the Illinois Institute of Technology. This building opened in 1963 and the collection was housed there until 1981. By the late 1970s the collection had once again expanded beyond the capacity of its building. On April 13, 1981 an agreement was reached between the Crerar Library Board of Directors and the University of Chicago to consolidate the collection with the University of Chicago's science collection.
A new building was constructed on the University of Chicago campus to house the consolidated collection and opened on September 10, 1984. The structure was designed by Stubbins Associates of Cambridge, Massachusetts, and has 160,836 square feet of floor space, costing $22 million to build. It has capacity for 1.3 million volumes. This building currently houses the John Crerar Library collection.
Scope Note
The materials in this collection date from 1977 to 2009 with the majority dating between 1981 and 1985. The bulk of the collection relates to the construction of the library building at the University of Chicago campus. This includes copies of construction contracts, floorplans and construction drawings, technical information relating to the construction materials and products, data from site surveys and reports, and Schedule B's from the construction process. There is also a small amount of meeting minutes and memoranda relating to the planning and execution of the collection merger. Additionally, the collection contains trace sheets and dealer information from 1982 to 1983 for missing Crerar material. The collection is divided into five series.
Series I, John Crerar Library Construction, contains materials relating to the planning and construction of the John Crerar Library building on the University of Chicago campus. Materials date from 1977 to 1985 and are arranged topically. Planning documents are first, followed by construction records arranged alphabetically within the groupings of subcontractor, materials and products, reports, meetings, and scheduling. Researchers should refer to Series IV for oversized blueprints and engineering drawings relating to construction.
The majority of files in Series I represent the work product of the primary contractor, Schal Associates, and their exchanges with their various subcontractors.
Series II, Missing Books Information, contains processing paperwork from the John Crerar Library missing book file. The majority of the materials are related to the 1980-1982 collection inventory carried out in connection with the prosecution of Joseph Putnam. Putnam was arrested in January 1983 and sentenced to two years in federal prison for the systematic theft and resale of rare books from the John Crerar Library. The books, sold through John Howell Books to various academic institutions and private collectors, were worth an estimated $330,000. The processing paperwork provides metadata for materials published within the 1828-1984 data range. Series II also contains copies of index cards for missing books and a book plate. Materials are arranged alphabetically by author name.
Series III, Audio-Visual, contains 2 compact discs from the Kathleen A Zar Symposium at the University of Chicago in 2009.
Series IV, Oversized, contains oversized construction drawings, blueprints, and building plans from the planning and construction of the John Crerar Library building at the University of Chicago. Materials are arranged alphabetically within each box, under the categories of subcontractor, materials and products, reports, and plans. Researchers should refer to Series I for related non-oversized materials. This series also contains a plaque from the John Crerar Library Director’s Office and a large scrapbook of photographs of the library.
Related Resources
The following related resources are located in the Department of Special Collections:
http://www.lib.uchicago.edu/e/spcl/select.html
Crerar Library. Records
Crerar Manuscripts. Collection
Crerar Library Collection of Patent Medicines
Crerar, Adams & Co. Collection
University of Chicago. Department of Buildings and Grounds. Records
University of Chicago. Library. Records
Subject Headings
Howell, Warren R.; Putnam, Joseph; University of Chicago. John Crerar Library; Libraries; Book thefts--United States
INVENTORY
- Series I: John Crerar Library Construction
  - Planning – Ad Hoc Committee on the John Crerar Library Building Program – Memoranda & Draft Agreements, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Planning – Ad Hoc Committee on the John Crerar Library Building Program – Memoranda, Construction Proposals and Funding Application Drafts, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Planning – Ad Hoc Committee on the John Crerar Library Building Program – Memoranda, Reports and Agreements, 1980-1981 [1/2] (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Planning – Ad Hoc Committee on the John Crerar Library Building Program – Memoranda, Reports and Agreements, 1980-1981 [2/2] (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Planning – University of Chicago Office of Physical Planning and Construction, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Planning – University of Chicago Office of Physical Planning and Construction, 1984 [1/2] (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Planning – University of Chicago Office of Physical Planning and Construction, 1984 [2/2] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Planning – University of Chicago Office of Physical Planning and Construction, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Consultants – Norton Services and Consulting Corporation, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Consultants – STS Consultants, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Contractor – Schal Associates – Memoranda, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Contractor – Schal Associates – Schedule B's, 1982-1984 [1/4] (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Contractor – Schal Associates – Schedule B's, 1982-1984 [2/4] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Contractor – Schal Associates – Schedule B's, 1982-1984 [3/4] (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Contractor – Schal Associates – Schedule B's, 1982-1984 [4/4] (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Contractor – Schal Associates – Transmittals, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – A & H Flood Engineering, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Accurate Partitions Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Advent Construction Co., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Alcan United Concrete, 1982-1984 [1/2] (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Alcan United Concrete, 1982-1983 [2/2] (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Alcan United Construction – Inryko Mill Test Reports, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Alsip Ornamental Iron, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Andrew McCann Lawn Sprinkler Company, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Bergalund Construction, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Blackhawk Paving Company, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Bradford Systems, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Caesar Fiocchi Company, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Chicago Metallic Corporation – Ceilings System Workbook, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Clauss Brothers, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Cold Springs Granite, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Commonwealth Edison, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Construction Specialities, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Custom Enclosures, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – C – Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – DiPietro Plumbing, 1983-1985 [1/7] (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – DiPietro Plumbing, 1983-1985 [2/7] (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – DiPietro Plumbing, 1983-1985 [3/7] (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – DiPietro Plumbing, 1983-1985 [4/7] (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – DiPietro Plumbing, 1983-1985 [5/7] (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – DiPietro Plumbing, 1983-1985 [6/7] (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – DiPietro Plumbing, 1983-1985 [7/7] (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Domiteaux Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Du-Al Floor Company, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Dwyer Products Company, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – D – Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Edward Stauber Wholesale Hardware, 1983 [1/5] (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Edward Stauber Wholesale Hardware, 1983 [2/5] (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Edward Stauber Wholesale Hardware, 1983 [3/5] (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Edward Stauber Wholesale Hardware, 1983 [4/5] (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Edward Stauber Wholesale Hardware, 1983 [5/5] (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Engineering Erection Company Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Environmental Systems Design, 1982-1984 [1/2] (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Environmental Systems Design, 1982-1984 [2/2] (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Esko & Young Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – F.E. Moran, 1983 [1/7] (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – F.E. Moran, 1983 [2/7] (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – F.E. Moran, 1983 [3/7] (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – F.E. Moran, 1983 [4/7] (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – F.E. Moran, 1983 [5/7] (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – F.E. Moran, 1983 [6/7] (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – F.E. Moran, 1983 [7/7] (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Forest Security Services, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Griffin Dewatering Corp, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Galloy & Van Etten, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Gage-Babcock & Associates, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Hajak Equipment Co., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Harding and Cogswell, 1982-1984 [1/2] (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Harding and Cogswell, 1982-1984 [2/2] (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Harding and Cogswell, 1982-1984 [3/3] (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Hastings Pavement Co., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Heitman & Associates Inc., 1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Hueler Tile, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Hugh Stubbins & Associates Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – IBG International, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – IBG International – Structural Calculations, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Illinois Bell Telephone, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Illinois Products, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – International Test & Balance, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – I – Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Johnson Controls Inc., 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – JR Smith Plumbing Company, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – K & K Enterprises, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Latronica & Sons, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Levy Company, 1983-1985 [1/4] (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Levy Company, 1983-1985 [2/4] (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Levy Company, 1983-1985 [3/4] (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Levy Company, 1983-1985 [4/4] (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – LeMessurier Associates/SCI, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Library Bureau Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Litgen Concrete Cutting, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Lowlor Ornamental Steel, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Loebl, Schlossman and Hackl, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Loebl, Schlossman and Hackl, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Loebl, Schlossman and Hackl, 1985 [1/2] (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Loebl, Schlossman and Hackl, 1985 [2/2] (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Loebl, Schlossman and Hackl – Drawings & Bulletins, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Maddock Mechanical, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Mansfield & Sons, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Maund Richards & Associates, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Midwest Caulking, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Moesler Book Depositories, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Montgomery Elevator Company, 1983 [1/2] (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Montgomery Elevator Company, 1983 [2/2] (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – M – Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – National Plumbing and Heating Supply, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Peoples Gas, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Premier Electric Company, 1983 [1/3] (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Premier Electric Company, 1983 [2/3] (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Premier Electric Company, 1983 [3/3] (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Premier Electric Company, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Premier Electric Company – Handbook, 1984 [1/4] (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Premier Electric Company – Handbook, 1984 [2/4] (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Premier Electric Company – Handbook, 1984 [3/4] (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Premier Electric Company – Handbook, 1984 [4/4] (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Professional Service Industries Inc., 1983 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – P – Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Satellite Industries, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Schmidt Iron Works, 1983 [1/3] (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Schmidt Iron Works, 1983 [2/3] (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Schmidt Iron Works, 1983 [3/3] (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Space Control Corp., 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – S – Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Thatcher Engineering, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Trainer Glass Co., 1983 [1/2] (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Trainer Glass Co., 1983 [2/2] (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Walter Ingstrup Co., 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Woodwork Corporation, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Subcontractors – Western Waterproofing Corp., 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – 3M Book Detection System, 1978-1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Acoustics, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Architectural Signage, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Aluminum Entrances and Steel Fronts, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Book Depository, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Cabinet Heaters Forced Flow, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Carpentry (Finish), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Carpentry (Rough), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Cement Plaster & Wallboard, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Ceramic Tile, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Chalkboards & Coat Hooks, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Concrete Mix Designs, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Concrete Transmittals, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Concrete Unit Masonry, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Concrete Work, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Curtain Walls and Windows, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Custom Enclosures, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Dock Lifts, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Duct Silencers & Duct Scalers, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Elevators, 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – General Electric Equipment, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Fire Extinguisher Cabinets, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Fire Protection, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Fireshutters, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Sprayed Fireproofing, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Furnishings, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Hardware, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Hardware Descriptions, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Hollow Metal Doors & Frames, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Hot Water Pumps & Converters, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Insulation, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Interior Glazing, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Johnson Control Dampers, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Kitchen Equipment & Appliances, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Kitchen Staff Lounge, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Louvers, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Metal Fabrications, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Metal Siding, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Moisture Protection, 1981-1984 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Precast Pavers, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Precast Plank, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Premolded Vapour Barrier, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Quadrangle Water Pipes, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Resilient Tile, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Runtal Radiation, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Roofing, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Sculptures, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Skylights, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Sound and Vibration Isolation, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Stacks and Shelving, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Steel Staivs, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Reinforcing Steel, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Structural Steel, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Stone, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Stone – Indiana Limestone Institute of America Handbook, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Toilet Accessories, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Tunnel Structural Conduit, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Wall Coverings, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Construction – Materials and Products – Window Glass, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Construction – Meetings – Landscaping 1984 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Construction – Meetings – Limestone & Steel Coordination Meeting, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Construction – Meetings – Mechanical Coordination, 1983-85 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Construction – Meetings – Mechanical On-Site Electrical Meetings, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Construction – Meetings – Progress Meeting Agenda, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Construction – Meetings – Safety and Job Coordination, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Construction – Meetings – Schal Associates, 1982-1985 [1/2] (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Construction – Meetings – Schal Associates, 1982-1985 [2/2] (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Construction – Punch Lists, 1984 [1/3] (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Construction – Punch Lists, 1984 [2/3] (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Construction – Punch Lists, 1984 [3/3] (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Construction – Final Punch List, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Construction – Reports – A & H Flood Engineering – January, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Construction – Reports – A & H Flood Engineering – February to March, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Construction – Reports – A & H Flood Engineering – March to April, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)